

Pablo Vallejo

BlockChain / Web Developer

Phone: (+34) 637 724 846 | Email: pablovallejo.gon@gmail.com

About Me

I am a 23 years old Spanish developer. Actually living in Barcelona and interested in remote work. Driving licence B (+5 years). I consider myself an enterprising person with initiative and facility to work in a team. +5 years of personal experience in web development. +2 years of experience into Ethereum(EVM) BlockChain. 4 years of professional customer service experience. Adaptable to Agile methodologies (SCRUM).

Curriculum Site chaoticbcn.com
GitHub and Linkedin at chaoticbcn.com/#contact

Experience

Pablo's CV • chaoticbcn.com • Barcelona, ESP•2020 – Present

Initialy was a project to promote crypto study and AI. Back-end(ExpressJS), Front-end(ES6).

Now is my personal curriculum were I posted three apps to show my skills.

SEO, domain, Rest-APIs implementation, server-side rendering

Back-end(NextJS), component based Front-end(ReactJS).

Web Developer • Autoescola Maragall • Barcelona, ESP•2015 – 2017

UI design, SEO positioning, bug rendering, client attention.

Domain and server creation/maintenance.

Education

Technological Baccalaureate

Joan Pelegrí Barcelona, ESP 2014-2016

ESO

Escola Solc Barcelona, ESP 2010-2014

Coding Languages

Python C



JavaScript(ES6)
Solidity



HTML5 & CSS3

JSX - Babel (React)

